The following programme contains
strong language. violence
and scenes. which some
viewers may find distressing.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(DRAMATIC NOTE)
♪ HOT CHOCOLATE:
You Sexy Thing ♪
♪ I believe in miracles
♪ Where you from?
♪ You sexy thing
♪ Sexy thing. you
♪ I believe in miracles
♪ Since you came along
♪ You sexy thing...
(UPBEAT INSTRUMENTAL)
(SONG CONTINUES
FAINTLY ON STEREO)
What do you believe in. Carlos?
(IN SPANISH)
Yeah. you do.
You hablo ingles.
You hablo ingles bueno.
(IN SPANISH)
Huh? (CHUCKLES)
♪ Yesterday I was one
of the lonely people
I believe in love.
Love's the only thing
we've got. mate.
Two people.
Connection.
(ENGINE REVS)
(SOUND DISTORTS)
(CRASHING & SCRAPING)
(CREAKING & SQUEAKING)
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
(LOW TECHNO MUSIC)
(DRAMATIC NOTE)
(FAINT. INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What are you doin'?
You know who we are? You
know who we work for?
(SHOUTS IN ARABIC)
(SPEAKS ARABIC)
(IN ARABIC)
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
Make peace with your God.
You're English?
(PANTING) Can you speak to them?
Tell them I work for the
cartel. From Guinea-Bissau!
This is our route!
It's your time.
Accept it.
Make peace with your God.
Pray.
I'm a drug trafficker.
I don't fuckin' pray!
(BIRD SQUAWKS) And it's
not my time to die.
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(PANTING)
Come on. mate.
Where you from back home?
Who are you?
Nah. nah. nah. please no!
Please! I don't wanna die.
Don't kill me! (GUNFIRE)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(PANTING) (TENSE MUSIC)
Get them in the truck! NOW!
(GASPS)
Hurry up!
In the back!
Let's go!
(PANTING) (GRUNTS)
In! There's something
I need to get.
Get in the fuckin' cab!
Please. It's just a photo.
It's in my car.
If you're lying. I'll kill you.
(TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
See?
Move!
Let's go! Let's go!
Get in the fuckin' car.
(GRUNTS)
Drive! Where to?
Just. Fuckin'. Drive!
(ENGINE REVS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
♪ RADIOHEAD: Bodysnatchers ♪
(DRAMATIC ROCK MUSIC)
♪ I do not
♪ Understand
♪ What it is
♪ I've done wrong
♪ Full of holes
♪ Check for pulse
(DRAMATIC ROCK INSTRUMENTAL)
♪ It is the 21st century
♪ Oh. the lines
Wrapped around my face
♪ Are for anyone else to see
♪ I'm a lie ♪
(DRAMATIC ROCK INSTRUMENTAL)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(DRAMATIC NOTE)
(WIND SWIRLING)
(IN RUSSIAN)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(IN RUSSIAN)
OKSANA:
Mm-hmm.
(IN RUSSIAN)
(TENSE NOTE)
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
(INHALES)
(GULPS)
(SIGHS)
Where were you
taking your cargo?
(SIGHS) Beirut.
I thought you'd go to Libya.
Your drugs are for
Europe. aren't they?
Usually. But not today.
We came from Bissau. through
Mali. into Algeria now.
Then Libya. Then a plane
takes me to Beirut.
(SIGHS)
This isn't the usual trip.
Keep going to Libya.
but not to your plane.
Take me to Benghazi.
I can't take you to
Benghazi. You will.
Because I just saved your life.
You owe me.
(SIGHS)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC)
Are these Gendarmes or military?
Gendarmes. I think.
You know them?
Cartel pays them too?
(TENSE MUSIC)
If you get me through here. maybe
you can keep some of your shipment.
Don't get out the car.
Don't say a word.
(TENSE MUSIC BUILDS)
(ENGINE REVS)
You give me up.
I'll shoot you through
the back of the seat.
In the fuckin' spine.
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(ENGINE REVS)
(RATTLING & CLICKING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(SHOUTS)
(MUSIC SOFTENS)
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
Captain Sebti.
Max. From Bissau.
(IN FRENCH)
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
Er. we. um...
...nous... er. meeting...?
(ACCENTED) Les
militants. Islamiques.
(IN FRENCH) Oui.
(FAINTLY) Les militants
attaquent nous.
Er... Pow. pow. pow!
Er. I'auto...
My I'auto...
Got fucked up.
I had to take this truck.
(CHUCKLES)
Mi companero. Carlos...
Mort.
It was a fuckin'
cauchemar. mate.
Cauchemar.
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
Pour toi.
For you.
(TENSE NOTE)
(NOTE FADES)
(UPBEAT TECHNO MUSIC)
OK.
(LIVELY MUSIC)
(IN FRENCH)
(LIVELY MUSIC CONTINUES)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
(PANTING)
What?
Max. yeah?
Yeah. What's wrong with that?
Nothin'.
Max. (CHUCKLES)
So. you think you're
Mad Max. do you. Max?
Driving around the desert.
delivering drugs.
doing mad shit. yeah?
No. I don't.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS. SNIFFS)
What's your name?
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC FADES IN)
Drive.
(TENSE MUSIC ENDS)
AK ammo only. 7.6.
One side fired and
it wasn't the Narcos.
Our jihadi's not here.
Alright. Sherlock. I ken
he's no fuckin' here.
Hijack. kill the Narcos.
steal their gear.
and then a fallout.
He shot his own fucking people.
Told ya. This cunt's evil.
No loyalty to anyone.
He's a fucking snake.
Bugs out north. Benghazi. maybe?
We nearly had him.
Been after this cunt for years.
It's only a matter of time. huh.
Alright. so what now?
A brew.
There's a storm comin'.
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC BUILDS)
(DRAMATIC NOTE. MUSIC ENDS)
(HORSE BRAYS)
(GRUNTS)
(IN KURDISH)
(SAND SWIRLING)
(ENGINE SLOWS)
Keep going.
I can't see the track.
(WIND SWIRLING)
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
When do you have to get
your plane to Beirut?
Tomorrow night.
What happens if you miss it?
I'll get killed.
That's not good.
(SLURPS LOUDLY)
So. are you a jihadi. then?
You don't even understand
what the word jihad means.
I know what it means.
Find someone who doesn't believe
what you believe and kill 'em.
No.
Jihad just means struggle.
(SLURPS)
Could be anything.
Making a living.
raising a family.
Personal struggles
each of us has
with the tests that Allah
sends us through our lives.
So that was a test
today. was it. from God?
When you shot your mates?
The choices you make in
trying to overcome the tests
determine whether you're one of
the righteous or one of the damned.
Why'd you shoot 'em?
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm one of the damned.
And you... (CLEARS THROAT)
You're a delivery driver.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah. you could've
worked for Amazon.
They don't pay as good as this.
And I'm not a delivery driver.
(SIGHS) I'm a drug trafficker.
You're a fucking
delivery driver. mate.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Accept the facts.
It's not just drugs I smuggle.
No?
Nah.
I smuggle antiquities too.
That's what I'm
going to Beirut for.
What antiquities?
Statues.
Statues?
(LIVELY. FUNKY MUSIC PLAYING)
Small statues. Very valuable.
The payment is the shipment.
You go to Beirut.
and get the statues.
Then you take them to Marrakesh.
Morocco? Why Morocco?
Why the questions. Max?
I just wanna know
what I'm doing. Danny.
You do what I tell you to do.
The statues have to be
transported separately.
Two statues.
You and Carlos. Two men.
Why have they gotta
be taken separately?
Because that's what
Antonio Alam wants.
He's the boss.
(IN SPANISH)
You want a girl
before you go. Max?
Nah. man.
Cheers. though. I'm alright.
(INDISTINCT. LIVELY
CHATTER OUTSIDE)
(GROANS)
(WIND SWIRLING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(SIGHS)
Did you sleep?
Nah.
I don't sleep much.
(SIGHS)
(BELT RATTLING) That's not good.
Clean the windows.
Thought you was praying at first
when I saw you outside the car.
Given up praying.
Why'd you try and
make me pray then.
back when you were
gonna kill me?
People like to pray
when they're gonna die.
Well. I don't believe in God.
Religion. None of that shit.
And what do you believe?
I believe in love.
Who do you love?
I love my girlfriend.
She's nice. right?
You're punching.
(LAUGHS)
That's what I tell her.
The moment I saw her.
I just knew.
What's her name. your girl?
Laetitia.
She in Guinea-Bissau?
Nah.
Nah. she's in Spain.
I had to come out here
for the cartel. For work.
So where you from? You're
from up north. yeah?
(SCOFFS) Fuckin' hell.
you're hard work.
You're English.
You can admit that. Not anymore.
What do you mean?
I'm stateless. No passport.
What. so you can't go back home?
Ever?
Never. (BIRD SQUAWKS)
(UNSETTLING NOTE)
What you looking for?
Nothing.
You sure?
Get in.
In.
(FAST. UPBEAT GUITAR MUSIC)
♪ SALIF KEITA: Madan ♪
(CHOIR SINGING IN BAMBARA)
♪ O laka la mm a le
♪ O laka la mm a le dja
♪ O laka la mm a le...
♪ Tama yoo pabba yo
♪ Tama yoo o' pabba
ho fago pib'ee...
Why do you wanna go
to Benghazi. then?
Benghazi's a place to disappear.
That what you want?
All you need to know is
you're taking me to Benghazi.
Yeah. I know I'm
taking you to Benghazi.
But all I wanna say is that
there's an oasis the Bedouin use.
I could take you there and you'd
get a lift to Benghazi from there.
If you want? You're
taking me to Benghazi.
Yes. for sure.
It's not a problem.
♪ Ori tali ma je'ye ♪
(SONG ENDS)
(GOATS BLEATING)
(DOG BARKS)
(ANIMALS CHITTERING)
(IN ARABIC)
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
You gonna tell me
your name. then?
No.
You're not Jihadi John. are you?
He's dead. Oh. yeah.
Yep. that's right.
(SINGING) ♪ Jihadi John
♪ Is fuckin' dead
♪ They dropped a bomb
On his fuckin' head ♪
You talk a lot. don't ya?
I just wanna know what
to call you. mate.
I could call you
Jihadi John Two?
I'll call you JJ.
No. you won't. (SIGHS)
If you don't tell
me. I'll have to.
I'll have no choice. Slow down.
(LOW. TENSE NOTE)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
What you doing?
We need petrol.
(SPITS)
What do you think happened?
They got killed.
By people like you?
Maybe.
Or maybe the people that were
smuggling them killed 'em.
Get any? A little.
We'll need more. OK. let's go.
(SOFT CLANG) I'm not
sure how far we'll get-
(TENSE NOTE)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC BUILDS SLOWLY)
(MUSIC STOPS) (GASPS)
(PANTING) It's OK.
It's OK.
Let's get this cleaned up. son.
(SIGHS) Then we'll
get you some scran.
You don't know what the
fuck I'm sayin'. do ya?
Well. whatever you speak.
this is fuckin'
gonna hurt like fuck.
(SCREAMS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ RACHID TAHA: Ya Rayah ♪
(SONG CONTINUES
FAINTLY ON STEREO)
We still need more fuel.
I told you. I know an
oasis. It's nearby.
We can take him there. and then
with the money in that rucksack.
you could pay to get him to
Europe. Then I can go to Beirut.
I can still make my plane.
(SONG CONTINUES)
OK. Go there.
(SIGHS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC GETS LOUDER)
(SONG CONCLUDES)
(HORNS HONKING)
(TENSE NOTES)
(INDISTINCT.
OVERLAPPING GREETINGS)
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(INDISTINCT)
(UNSETTLING NOTE)
(READER PULSING)
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(OMINOUS NOTE)
(SIGHS)
(DRAMATIC NOTE) They are ready.
MAN (IN ARABIC):
(WIND SWIRLING)
(IN ARABIC)
(SOMBRE MUSIC)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DRAMATIC NOTE)
(CLUCKING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(SIGHS)
How are you doing this?
Is there someone behind me?
(INDISTINCT)
So?
There are Bedouin here that
can take him to Benghazi.
And then what? They sell him
in a fuckin' slave market?
He has a chance to get
to Europe from there.
You can go too.
I'm not going with him.
Then a chance is all
you can give him.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
OK. son. You're on
your own now. yeah?
I'm sorry I can't
do no more for ya.
Try and survive.
Hey.
Hurry up. we need to leave.
Make space!
(GRUNTS. INDISTINCT)
No. no. no. What you doing?
No. no. no. Stop. Stop!
Go.
Fuck off!
(SOMBRE MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
Come on.
Let's go.
(FAINT. INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Wait!
(GENTLE MUSIC FADES IN)
(SINGS IN PULAAR) ♪
Bandiraabe aree mballee kam
♪ Mballee kam
ALL: ♪ Yee yi walloo
♪ Bandiraabe aree
mballee kam. mballee kam
♪ Yee yi walloo ♪
(SINGING CONTINUES FAINTLY)
Do you kill some kids
or something. before?
Shoot one?
Strap one up with a
suicide bomb. or something?
Yeah. that makes sense.
You're trying to save this
kid to make up for it.
I told you. God sends us tests.
Fuckin' right he does.
You need to make your mind up.
We can't stay here forever.
Tomorrow I'll go to Benghazi.
You go your way.
Deliver your drugs.
Go to Beirut.
I'm gonna take the
money from the rucksack
and make sure he gets to Europe.
If you're sure.
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(INSECTS CHIRRUPING)
Thank you for not killing me.
That's OK.
I do owe you for that.
(DISTANT SHOUTING & SCREAMING)
(GUNSHOT)
(BOTH PANTING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(GUNFIRE) (SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
Go!
(ENGINE SPLUTTERING)
Come on. you piece of shit.
Move! I'm trying. mate!
(ENGINE REVS) Come on!
(TENSE MUSIC)
(MEN SHOUTING IN ARABIC)
(BANGING)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(MUSIC BUILDS)
(MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY)
(PANTING)
(IN ARABIC)
(OMINOUS NOTE SWELLS)
(CLATTER)
(INSECTS CHIRRUPING)
(SIGHS)
(IN ARABIC)
(GUN CLICKS)
(SCREAMS) Aghhhh! (GUNFIRE)
Aghhhh!
Aghhhhhhhh! (GRUNTING)
(PANTING) (BULLET RICOCHETS)
(GUNFIRE) Aghhhh!
Aghhhhhhh! Aghhhh!
(GRUNTS) (GASPS)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(SOMBRE MUSIC)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(SOMBRE MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING & GUNFIRE)
(DRAMATIC. SOMBRE MUSIC)
(MUFFLED GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(DRAMATIC. SOMBRE
MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC CRESCENDOS.
STOPS ABRUPTLY)
(PANTING. GRUNTS)
(DISTANT GUNFIRE)
(SOMBRE. DRAMATIC NOTE)
(PANTING)
(IN ARABIC)
(GROANS)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(SOMBRE MUSIC)
(WIND SWIRLS)
(EXHALES SHAKILY)
(SOMBRE MUSIC FADES)
(SIGHS)
We should've let him
go with the Bedouin.
Nah. I should've left
him in the truck.
(PANTING)
It was written for
him to die there.
Nothing's written.
Everything is written!
I'll know when it's
my time to die.
And so will you.
(LOW. SOMBRE MUSIC)
(PANTING)
The shipment's gone.
They burned all of it.
I was gonna use that
to pay for the statues that
my boss bought in Beirut.
So don't go Beirut.
Go somewhere else.
Lose a shipment. the
cartel hunt you down.
I work for them.
I have no choice.
Maybe they'll think
you died in the ambush?
This could be your
chance to disappear.
You can run. but you can't hide.
You ran when the
shooting started.
And you hid under a truck.
Are you a coward. Max? Huh?
Are you afraid of violence?
You're in the drugs game and
you're scared of violence?
I'm a driver. I
don't kill people.
I don't need to.
And I won't.
I'm not like you.
You kill everybody you meet.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(SPADE CLATTERS)
I didn't kill you.
And why didn't you kill me?
(TENSE. SOMBRE MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
Nah. come on. tell me.
You could've killed me.
You could've taken the coke.
the money. whatever you wanted.
But you changed your mind.
You looked up at the sky
and you changed your mind.
What was it? What
was it. a sign?
A sign? Yeah. a sign.
From-From Allah! Whatever!
What was it?
It was a drone.
A drone?
Like that one.
Run!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Oh. I've got you
now. cunty baws.
(LAUGHS)
Drone? A fuckin' drone?
I thought maybe you saw
an angel. or something.
Can't see angels. Just drones.
What you doin'? Can't outrun it.
(TENSE MUSIC)
(GUNSHOT)
Fuck.
What's wrong? The sun!
Fuck!
No.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(LAUGHS)
Come on!
(YELLS) Argh!
I thought you said you
didn't pray anymore!
(SIGHS. MUTTERS IN ARABIC)
(WHISPERING. ECHOES)
(OMINOUS NOTE)
(DRONE BUZZING)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(WHISPERING & BUZZING INTENSIFY)
(CRUNCH) (BUZZING & MUSIC STOPS)
Fuck's sake!
Don't stop! I can see them!
(SIGHS)
(SCOFFS) What was it?
A bird.
(SIGHS) An eagle.
(TENSE MUSIC FADES IN)
Go! OK.
Let's see how well you
motherfuckers know the desert.
(ENGINE REVS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Fuckin' go! Go! Go! Go!
So. who were they? Who's after ya?
I don't know. Someone with a drone.
Who the fuck has drones? Lots
of people. they're cheap!
It's armies that have
drones. (BANGING)
For fuck's sake!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(MUSIC FADES)
Think we shook them
off? I don't see 'em.
Maybe that bird was a sign.
The eagle. A sign from God.
About what?
That you should come to Beirut
with me and get them statues.
I'm not going to Beirut.
Where else are you gonna go?
I don't know. (WHISPERS) Fuck.
And it's a two man
job. Me and Carlos.
The guy you killed.
So maybe you owe me and should be
there in case I need a bit of help?
I don't owe you anything.
(ENGINE REVS)
Very simple job. Very quick.
In and out. You and me.
That bird wasn't a sign from
God that I have to go to Beirut.
No. But it answered
your prayers.
(SNIFFS)
How are you getting there?
(UPBEAT RHYTHM)
(LIVELY INSTRUMENTAL)
♪ ANDRE SOUEID FT.
YVES YOUNES: Siraa ♪
(MUSIC LULLS)
(SIGHS)
Idir!
My friend.
We're flying in that?
Through the night?
Yeah. You can get a kip on the
way. We'll be there by morning.
(LIVELY INSTRUMENTAL RESUMES)
(MUSIC LULLS) We were attacked.
We lost the shipment.
which is true.
But I'll say you saved me.
The cartel are
sending another cargo.
but we still need to take
the statues and leave.
Do you think they'll buy that?
Yeah. why not?
No one from the
cartel will be there.
And I'm very
plausible. Plausible?
Are you?
(UPBEAT RHYTHM CONTINUES)
(LIVELY INSTRUMENTAL RESUMES)
(MUSIC SOFTENS)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
Salut.
WOMAN: Bonjour. Er.
c'est en bas. a gauche.
Merci.
In and out. remember?
And leave the talking
to me. Yeah. yeah.
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(OMINOUS NOTE)
Danny! (SCOFFS SOFTLY)
What you doing here?
We heard you hit some trouble.
(TENSE NOTE)
Yeah.
We ran into some jihadis.
They took the shipment.
And Carlos didn't make it.
(OMINOUS NOTE)
Why did I have to hear
this from the Gendarmes?
Why not you?
I lost my phone.
How was I meant to talk to you?
And I wanted to stick to
the schedule. you know?
Get the statues for Alam.
I knew it was important.
It is important but how
were you gonna pay for
the statues without
the shipment?
And who the fuck is this?
This is JJ. He saved my life.
He saved your life?
That's not my name.
But I did save his life.
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(GRUNTS) Danny. come on.
Please. mate! You
can't kill him in here.
Get out of the way.
(DRAMATIC NOTE) Drop it. Danny.
Max. what the fuck are
you doing? I mean it!
Tell him to drop his as well!
(LOW. TENSE MUSIC)
What are you gonna do. Max?
Are you gonna kill me?
You fucking coward.
You gonna shoot me?
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(YELLS) (GRUNTS)
(YELPS. GROANS)
Fucking hell!
Hijo de puta! (PANTS)
Thank you.
Where are the statues?
(OMINOUS NOTE)
There's supposed
to be two of 'em.
Pack 'em up. We're taking 'em.
(GROANING) Don't fuckin'
look at him. Do it!
(GROANING)
You just tried to kill us. mate.
So we're taking your
fucking statues.
And if you want 'em back. you're
gonna have to pay us for 'em.
You're gonna fucking die. cono!
(CHUCKLES) We're
all gonna die. mate.
Get the other one.
(TENSE MUSIC)
Hurry up!
Don't fuckin' move.
(PANTING)
Don't take it. please.
Wait.
Keep them two metres apart.
Max! Come on!
Max.
(QUIETLY) We're not done.
(TENSE MUSIC)
(GUNSHOTS)
Your men can't shoot at them.
If you hit the bags
they might explode.
(SCREAMS) (GUNSHOTS)
Mierda! They have Uranium.
Nuclear fuel.
Enough to blow up
the whole city.
(TENSE MUSIC FADES)
(DRAMATIC ROCK GUITAR
MUSIC FADES IN)
♪ GUNS N' ROSES:
Welcome to the Jungle ♪
(ROCK INSTRUMENTAL BUILDS)
You told me it was gonna be a
quick job. In and fuckin' out.
Doctor Cassandra Bryce?
I'm with the Drug Enforcement
Agency here in Beirut.
I have some intelligence that needs
your particular nuclear expertise.
The fuck is that?
My name is Antonio Alam.
That's the boss of the cartel.
"Listen carefully. Max.
The metal in the
boxes is uranium."
My source said that it
was 50 kilos of uranium.
That could make a bomb.
Like a dirty bomb?
A Hiroshima-sized bomb.
(SONG CONTINUES) ♪
N-n-n-n-n-n-n-n knees. knees
♪ Oh. ah
♪ I wanna watch you bleed
♪ Welcome to the jungle
♪ We take it day by day
♪ If you want it.
you're gonna bleed
♪ But it's the price you pay
♪ And you're a very sexy girl
♪ Who's very hard to please
♪ You can taste
the bright lights
♪ But you won't
get there for free
♪ In the jungle
♪ Welcome to the jungle
♪ Feel my
♪
Sha-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na
♪ Knees. knees
♪ Down in the jungle
♪ Welcome to the jungle
♪ Watch it bring you to your
♪ It's gonna bring you down
♪ Huh! ♪
(SONG ENDS)
Subtitles by Sky Access Services
www.skyaccessibility.sky
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org